yesbitch.net 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy – Yes Bitch!

Parents: Please use one or more of the following systems to prevent your children from accessing this and other adult sites: [Cyber Patrol](http://www.cyberpatrol.com/) , [Net Nanny](http://www.netnanny.com/)

Your rights as a visitor to this web site

Thank you for visiting our web site. It’s very important to me to protect the personal privacy of individuals who use the Internet. If you have any questions or concerns about my Internet privacy policy, or any other issues involving the Internet, I want to hear about them and hope you will contact me to let me know your opinions.

The basic privacy policy for my Web site is simple: I don’t collect any personal information about you when you visit my site unless you choose to provide information to me, through e-mail or a request for my e-Newsletter, so that I can contact you about an issue you have raised or help you with a problem. Below I’ve posted a more detailed description of the type of information that may be collected when you visitmy web site and how that information is handled.  
Information Collected and Stored Automatically

We only collect data which your internet provider sends us. That’s the country you’re from and your ip.  
If You Send Us Personal Information

If you simply visit my Web site and do not email me or sign up for my e-Newsletter, my Web site does not collect any personal information about you. You can also contact me by e-mail using my Web site’s online web form to express your views or concerns or to ask for assistance with a particular problem involving a federal agency. The online Web form asks you for your name, address, and e-mail address. I use this information to follow up with you about the issue you wrote me.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To “opt-out,” please click here. http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx. Click here to find out more!

Contact

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy. Use the Contact Us page to submit your question.
